fashion.me 2013-09-09

# Fashion.me Privacy Policy

                                                   Fashion.me Privacy Policy
    This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Fashion.me, Inc. (“we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use
    and disclosure of your information on www.fashion.me (the “Site”) and the services, features, content or applications we
    offer (collectively with the Site, the “Services”). We receive information about you from various sources, including: (i) if
    you register for the Site and the Services, through your user account on the Services (your “Account”); (ii) your use of the
    Services generally; and (iii) from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the
    collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.
    What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?
    This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) gathered when you
    are using or accessing the Services. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of any Personal Information that our
    business partners share with us or that we share with our business partners.
    This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including but not limited
    to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you access through the Services or to
    individuals that we do not manage or employ. While we attempt to facilitate access only to those Third Party Services that
    share our respect for your privacy, we cannot take responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party
    Services. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of any Third Party Services you access through the
    Services.
    What Information Do We Collect?
    The information we gather enables us to personalize, improve and continue to operate the Services. In connection with
    certain aspects of the Services, we may request, collect and/or display some of your Personal Information. We collect the
    following types of information from our users.
    Account Information:
    When you create an Account, you will provide information that could be Personal Information, such as your username,
    password and email address. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on
    the Services and providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore may not
    be anonymous. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services. You may unsubscribe
    from these messages through your Account settings, although we, regardless, reserve the right to contact you when we
    believe it is necessary, such as for account recovery purposes. We collect information when you register for an Account on
    the Services by logging into an account that you already have with a Third Party Service (such as Facebook). If you create
    your Account by logging into a Third Party Service via the Site, you are using the Personal Information you have already
    provided to the Third Party Service (such as your email address and other information you make publicly available via the
    Third Party Service) to create your Account on the Site; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings with
    the Third Party Service, so please consult the Third Party Service’s privacy practices. We don’t actually store your
    passwords for those Third Party Services. Instead, we just use an authentication token to verify your user name.
    User Content:
    Some features of the Services allow you to provide content to the Services, such as written comments and photos. All
    content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your Account. We
    may continue to disclose such content to third parties in a manner that does not reveal Personal Information, as described in
    this Privacy Policy.
    Financial Information:
    We do not currently collect financial information, such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration
    date or other financial information); that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processing company
    (the “Payment Processor”), and use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable
    terms of service and privacy policy.
GDSVF&H\1497817.1

    Email Communications:
    We may receive a confirmation when you open an email from us. We use this confirmation to improve our customer
    service.
    Information Collected Using Cookies:
        Cookies are pieces of text that may be provided to your computer through your web browser when you access a
         website. Your browser stores cookies in a manner associated with each website you visit. We use cookies to enable our
         servers to recognize your web browser and tell us how and when you visit the Site and otherwise use the Services
         through the Internet.
        Our cookies do not, by themselves, contain Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information
         collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are. As noted, however, we do use
         cookies to identify that your web browser has accessed aspects of the Services and may associate that information with
         your Account if you have one.
        Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new
         cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of
         each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave cookies active, because they enable you
         to take advantage the most attractive features of the Services.
        This Privacy Policy covers our use of cookies only and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not
         control when or how third parties place cookies on your computer. For example, Third Party Services to which a link
         points may set cookies on your computer.
    Information Related to Advertising and the Use of Web Beacons:
    To support and enhance the Services, we may serve advertisements, and also allow third parties advertisements, through the
    Services. These advertisements are sometimes targeted and served to particular users and may come from third party
    companies called “ad networks.” Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and
    research firms.
    Advertisements served through the Services may be targeted to users who fit a certain general profile category may be
    based on anonymized information inferred from information provided to us by a user, including Personal Information (e.g.,
    gender or age), may be based on the Services usage patterns of particular users, or may be based on your activity on Third
    Party Services. We do not provide Personal Information to any ad networks for use outside of the Services.
    To increase the effectiveness of ad delivery, we may deliver a file (known as a “web beacon”) from an ad network to you
    through the Services. Web beacons allow ad networks to provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting
    for us and for advertisers. Web beacons also enable ad networks to serve targeted advertisements to you when you visit
    other websites. Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s
    servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.
    Aggregate Information:
    We collect statistical information about how both unregistered and registered users, collectively, use the Services
    (“Aggregate Information”). Some of this information is derived from Personal Information. This statistical information is
    not Personal Information and cannot be tied back to you, your Account or your web browser.
    How, and With Whom, Is My Information Shared?
    The Services are designed to help you share information with others. As a result, some of the information generated
    through the Services is shared publicly or with third parties.
GDSVF&H\1497817.1                                                  2

    Public Information about Your Activity on the Services:
    Some of your activity on and through the Services is public by default. This may include, but is not limited to, content you
    have posted publicly on the Site or otherwise through the Services.
    Registered users may have some of this information associated with their Accounts. Unregistered users will not have this
    association, but information concerning their use of the Services (such as what pages they have visited) may be tracked
    anonymously through the use of cookies and stored by us.
    Please also remember that if you choose to provide Personal Information using certain public features of the Services, then
    that information is governed by the privacy settings of those particular features and may be publicly available. Individuals
    reading such information may use or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your
    knowledge, and search engines may index that information. We therefore urge you to think carefully about including any
    specific information you may deem private in content that you create or information that you submit through the Services.
    IP Address Information:
    While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public. We do at times, however, share this
    information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise
    specified in this Privacy Policy.
    Information You Elect to Share:
    You may access Third Party Services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those Third Party Services
    from within the Site. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these Third Party Services, and you
    are responsible for reading and understanding those Third Party Services’ privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only
    governs information collected on the Services.
    Aggregate Information:
    We share Aggregate Information with our partners, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business.
    We share this type of statistical data so that our partners can understand how and how often people use our Services and
    their services or websites, which facilitates improving both their services and how our Services interface with them. In
    addition, these third parties may share with us non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal Information about you
    that they have independently developed or acquired.
    Email Communications with Us:
    As part of the Services, you may occasionally receive email and other communications from us, such as communications
    relating to your Account.
    User Profile Information:
    User profile information including your username and other information you enter may be displayed to other users to
    facilitate user interaction within the Services. We will not directly reveal user email addresses to other users.
    Financial Information:
    As stated above, we do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our
    Payment Processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our
    Payment Processor for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated through the Services, enrolling you in
    discount, rebate, and other programs in which you elect to participate, protecting against or identify possible fraudulent
    transactions, and otherwise as needed to manage our business.
    Information Shared with Our Agents:
    We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our
    control (our “Agents”). We may need to share Personal Information with our Agents in order to provide products or
GDSVF&H\1497817.1                                                   3

    services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other
    information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal
    Information with our Agents.
    Information Disclosed Pursuant to Business Transfers:
    In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the
    transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or
    enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You
    acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your Personal
    Information as set forth in this policy.
    Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others:
    We also reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to (i)
    satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce our Terms of Service, including
    investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (iv)
    respond to user support requests, or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes
    exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.
    Information We Share With Your Consent:
    Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will
    be able to prevent the sharing of this information.
    Is Information About Me Secure?
    Your Account information will be protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to prevent unauthorized
    access to your Account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting
    access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.
    We seek to protect Account information to ensure that it is kept private; however, we cannot guarantee the security of any
    Account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the
    security of user information at any time.
    We otherwise store all of our information, including your IP address information, using industry-standard techniques. We
    do not guarantee or warrant that such techniques will prevent unauthorized access to information about you that we store,
    Personal Information or otherwise.
    What Information of Mine Can I Access?
    If you are a registered user, you can access information associated with your Account by logging into the Services.
    Registered and unregistered users can access and delete cookies through their web browser settings.
    How Can I Delete My Account?
    Should you ever decide to delete your Account, you may do so by emailing help@fashion.me . If you terminate your
    Account, any association between your Account and information we store will no longer be accessible through your
    Account. However, given the nature of sharing on the Services, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion will
    remain stored on our servers and will remain accessible to the public.
    What Choices Do I Have Regarding My Information?
        You can always opt not to disclose certain information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of some
         of our features.
GDSVF&H\1497817.1                                                     4

        You can delete your Account. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to delete the Account,
         and activity generated prior to deletion will remain stored by us and may be publicly accessible.
    What Happens When There Are Changes to this Privacy Policy?
    We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in
    effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you
    by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy
    when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.
    What If I Have Questions or Concerns?
    If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy using the Services, please send us a detailed message to
    legal@fashion.me . We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
    Effective Date: January 01st, 2012
GDSVF&H\1497817.1                                                   5
